Jessica Wise

SUMMARY

UX Designer with a passion for delivering customer driven designs supported by a background of 4+ years as a Customer Success Advocate. Experience in all aspects of the design process from idea infancy to developer design handoff.

Looking to help companies grow and creatively evolve their products to meet internal and external client needs and expectations. Keenly interested in innovation-driven startups looking to make a footprint in the tech community.

EXPERIENCE

Fidelity Investments, Boston, MA — *UX Designer/Design Lead*

JUL 2018 - PRESENT

- Handle the UX Design process from project requirements to high fidelity prototyping for all projects and redesigns
- Present designs to stakeholders and business partners to ensure clear communication of project progress
- Ensure designs are technologically feasible with development teams
- Ensure designs follow brand standards by self assessment and working with Visual Designers
- Conduct usability testing both alone and with User Researchers
- Participate in sprint planning, backlog refinement, and sprint retro sessions
- Maintain ramp sheets to ensure project is not over budget and resource times are allocated correctly

StreetSmarts, Remote — Part Time UX Designer

APR 2018 - DEC 2018

- Handled the UX Design process from start to finish for all features and redesigns
- Conducted all user research via the facebook group or user interviews
- Designed mid to high fidelity wireframes and Invision prototypes
- Created technical documentation for wireframes to be handed off to engineers
- Participated in sprint planning sessions

Placester, **Inc.**, **Boston**, **MA** — Support UX Engineer

JAN 2018 - MAR 2018

- Managed onboardings and client happiness for a Book of Business that consisted of Real Estate Agents and Brokers of varying technical background
- Exceeded client expectations by providing HTML and CSS skills along with JS knowledge to better customize the templated solution to match clients' personal branding and website needs
- Assisted with internal testing of CSS and JS changes made to templates
- Assisted clients and coworkers with editing of logos and pictures to better fit within the templated websites
- Understood client needs and expectations and achieved a 5 star CSAT survey rating for all months employed

173 Main St Apt 1 Malden, MA 02148 (413) 727-5977 jessica.lee.wise@gmail.com http://www.jessica-ux.design

EDUCATION

Columbus College of Art and Design (CCAD) Bachelor of Fine Arts in Animation 2012

General Assembly UX Design 2018

HIGHLIGHTS

Customer Oriented

Creative Thinker

Problem Solver

Able to work with all teams of varying sizes

Tech-savvy

KNOWLEDGE BASE

Visual Design

User Research

Usability Testing

HTML / CSS

Photoshop

Illustrator

Sketch

Invision

SCRUM/Agile

VueJS

ReactJS

Bootstrap

Jira